acyba.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Acyba.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring your data is protected. You can be assured that the personal information you provide when using this website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

If you don't agree with any modification then feel free to close your account. If you still use our services after the modifications, it means you agree with the new conditions.

Acyba.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page to ensure that you agree with any changes. This policy is effective from May 23rd, 2018.

### Consent

Subscribing to our website and using our services means you agree with both this privacy policy and the use of Cookies.  
You can refuse them or ask us to modify/delete your data at any moment. Simply let us know via our contact form or the email address [support@acyba.com](mailto:support@acyba.com).

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * **Subscription / Profile**  
During the subscription process we ask our users to provide us with some information such as name, username, email address, and password.  
Some other information are stored (Registration date, account confirmation date, IP used to register and IP used to confirm your account). These information are stored to be compliant with the GDPR and be able to check if there is any issue with someone's account.

  * **License Management    
**We save the license(s) you own, the website you've attached the license to (domain and cron URL), the order linked to your license, the purchase date, the expiration date, the AcyMailing level (Essential, Enterprise etc) you own and the number of times you've downloaded our products. These information need to be collected on our end in order to improve our support quality and to allow you to use some of our products' features (cron task, auto-updater, version checker...)

  * **Statistics**  
We use some cookies on our website, collect IP addresses and open statistics on our emails in order to improve our communication and see which kind of newsletter/information is the most appreciated by our community.

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address you provided and if you subscribed to our newsletters
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.  
In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we set up suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
None of your credit card information and/or Paypal account information are stored in any way by Acyba.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the websites in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

According to the law n°78-17 of the January 6th 1978 concerning the protection of persons concerning the processing of personal information and modified by the law n°2007-801 of the August 6th 2004 (BOEM 160* and 722),  the automated gathering, recording and conservation of the personal information on this website is done following a declaration of information handling to the Commission Nationale de l'Informatique et des Libertés (CNIL). Accordingly to the article 34 and following, you have the right to ask access and rectification of your personal information by e-mail at [support@acyba.com](mailto:support@acyba.com).
